In 1909, they entered the desert. Now, the truth will finally emerge.
The Last Manhunt is a western, crime, drama film directed by Christian Camargo.
In 1909, Willie Boy and his love Carlota go on the run after he accidentally
shoots her father in a confrontation gone terribly wrong.
With President Taft coming to the area, the local sheriff leads two Native
American trackers seeking justice for their “murdered” tribal leader.
Willie Boy, played by Martin Sensmeier.
Carlotta, played by Mainei Kinimaka.
Big Jim, played by Jason Momoa.
William Johnson, played by Zahn McClarnon.
Maria, played by Lily Gladstone.
Hyde, played by Raoul Max Trujillo.
The Last Manhunt is an American Western film, released in 2022.
It is directed by Christian Camargo and written by Thomas Pa'a
Sibbett from a story by Sibbett and Jason Momoa.
Momoa is also an executive producer.
The film stars Martin Sensmeier as Willie, alongside an ensemble cast including Momoa,
Camargo, Mainei Kinimaka, Lily Gladstone, Zahn McClarnon, and Raoul Max Trujillo.
In May 2022, it opened the Pioneertown International Film Festival.
Worldwide rights to the film were picked up by Saban Films in June 2022.
Other films have told the Paiute legend, including Tell Them
Willie Boy Is Here, starring Robert Redford.
The tone is emotional.